Hi everyone, today we are going to learn how to make furniture in Marvelous Designer.
Use the rectangle tool to create a 500mm x 300mm rectangle in the 2D window.
Then press and hold the edit tool to switch to the circular line tool, click and drag a point.
In the process of dragging, press and hold the right button to enter the number of corners.
The four corners are operated in the same way.
You can see that the plate has a thickness.
When creating a default particle frame, the distance between the points is relatively large, and there is not enough grid at the corner, which is not smooth enough.
If the particle frame is reduced to 3, the grid is relatively small, the number of grids is relatively large, and the transition is relatively smooth.
The height of the particle frame is slightly increased, and the distance between the points of direction is reduced.
If the particle frame is created, the thickness will be reduced, because the particle frame has been made by the texture surface.
The thickness of the particle frame is saved, then the thickness of the particle frame is adjusted, and the thickness of the particle frame is adjusted.
After applying the density of the signature, adjust the boundary bend green and the angle of the plate can be controlled.
The smaller the number, the sharper the number, and the larger the number, the smoother the number.
Now that we have assembled the chair and cushion with the panels, we need to convert these panels into OBJ.
When converting, you need to select the option to convert into OBJ, so that you can separate the cushion and chair.
Because later it will not be able to be wrapped on the outside of each part, so you need to separate these panels.
Convert the rest of the parts together.
To convert the rest of the parts, you need to select the option to convert into OBJ.
Now we have the table and the table is out of the way, you have to change the position of the table.
If all the panels are to be converted into OBJ, then when editing and moving, they are to be converted into OBJ.
Then we can't separate the panels.
We can separate and choose to move